

ĭtlo@sfu.ca | ☐ jeremy-jtlo | ☐ jeremy-lo-7131017b

Summary.

Currently, I'm a React developer at Microsoft Canada, but my previous experience includes Electronic Arts and BlackBerry. I am driven to solve problems by improving code maintainability and eliminating tech debt. My ideal work environment is one where I can challenge myself to constantly improve.

So if you need something built, I build things.

Work Experience

Microsoft Vancouver, Canada

SOFTWARE ENGINEER II May 2021 - PRESENT

- · Drive feature development by coordinating with designers, testers, and product managers across multiple timezones
- Review, triage, and debug live site issues for Microsoft Teams Rooms (MTR) customers
- Prototype and implement new features for Meeting Room consoles and front of room displays
- Create and maintain unit tests for UI components to prevent unnecessary regressions
- · Submit bug fixes to both the next-gen React and legacy Angular codebases for MS Teams

Electronic Arts Canada

Burnaby, Canada

WER DEVELOPER

Sep. 2017 - Mar. 2021

- Plan, scope, and implement new features for current and future releases of the FIFA Ultimate Team Companion apps (FUT19, FUT20).
- Oversaw integration of brand-new 'vanity' items to FUT User Clubs in FIFA20, including API call structure, asset automation, and view construction
- Managed Live Content responsibilities such as coordinating roll-outs of exclusive timed campaigns for FUT Companions.
- Rewrote legacy tools for parsing app metadata, from older Java and C# to Python.
- Prevented content leaks, cut build times by exposing and resolving issues in 2D asset pipeline.
- Interfaced with producers, developers, and testers across Live Content, Server, and Console teams. Facilitated communication between Canada and Romania engineering teams.

Electronic Arts Canada

Burnaby, Canada

ASSOCIATE TECHNICAL ARTIST

Jun. 2016 - Sep. 2017

- Wrote and supported existing Maya plugins and other packages used by artists on Rigging team, in C# and Python.
- Automated mass mesh weight transfers in C# Maya API.
- Collected, assessed, and prioritized feedback on plugins from users.
- Fixed visual bugs on assets and animations using node- and timeline-based editors in proprietary Frostbite engine.

Tantalus SystemsBurnaby, Canada

TEST AUTOMATION ENGINEER (CO-OP)

Jan. 2014 - Aug. 2014

- Discussed, planned, and executed web front-end features. Used Python Bottle, HTML/CSS, and Javascript to reduce setup time in regression testing of server features.
- Created a tool with Python Ixml and etree to send build e-mails that identify failed tests associated to closed JIRA issues.
- Managed Live Content responsibilities such as coordinating roll-outs of exclusive timed campaigns for FUT Companions.
- Met daily with teammates to sync progress and design future plans for automation.
- Managed Ubuntu and OEL VMs used as build machines and test environments.

BlackBerry Canada Waterloo, Canada

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (CO-OP)

Jan. 2013 - Aug. 2013

- · Oversaw deployment and automated testing of BES10 servers through Jenkins, Maven, Ant, and VMWare vSphere.
- · Created, deployed, and re-tooled scripts used for production and maintenance of build config files.
- Managed instances of test host machines using Windows Server and Ubuntu LTS virtual machines.
- Investigated, installed, and reviewed third-party plugins for Jenkins before deploying to Continuous Integration Team's production server.

Education

Simon Fraser University

Burnaby, Canada

Sep. 2010 - May. 2016

B.Sc. IN COMPUTING SCIENCE

• Graduated with a Minor in Interactive Art and Technology

APRIL 24, 2023 JEREMY LO · RÉSUMÉ 1